
export const questionnaireCardData = [
  { question: "Do you enjoy coming up with creative solutions to problems", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  { question: "Are you interested in the technical aspects of projects", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  { question: "Do you enjoy hands-on work and creating tangible things", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  { question: "Are you detail-oriented and prioritize quality", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  { question: "Do you like presenting and pitching your ideas to others", answer: "unanswered", tag: "leadership" },
  { question: "Are you comfortable taking risks and trying new approaches", answer: "unanswered", tag: "leadership" },
  { question: "Do you love keeping up with the latest technological advancements", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  { question: "Are you good at leading a team and guiding them towards goals", answer: "unanswered", tag: "leadership" },
  { question: "Are you curious about how products and systems work", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  { question: "Do you enjoy sketching, designing, and creating visual stuff", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  // { question: "Are you passionate about making a positive impact on society and the environment", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  // { question: "Can you handle juggling multiple tasks and deadlines at once", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  // { question: "Do you like analyzing data and making data-driven decisions", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  // { question: "Are you good at problem-solving and critical thinking", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  // { question: "Do you enjoy working with people and building relationships", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  // { question: "Are you comfortable with managing budgets and financial aspects", answer: "unanswered", tag: "leadership" },
  // { question: "Do you have a knack for identifying market trends and opportunities", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  // { question: "Are you interested in user experience and user behavior", answer: "unanswered", tag: "interest" },
  // { question: "Do you like organizing and planning projects from start to finish", answer: "unanswered", tag: "personality" },
  // { question: "Are you skilled at communication and negotiation", answer: "unanswered", tag: "leadership" }
];


export const careerDescriptionCardData = [
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Develop content such as graphics, web pages, logos, advertisements, or brochures." }, // Graphic Designer
  { tag: "Potential Task", description: "Research and conceptualize new product ideas, considering both form and function." }, // Industrial Designer
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Create wireframes, prototypes, and user interface designs for digital products." }, // UX/UI
  { tag: "Potential Task", description: "Analyze market trends and competition to identify potential growth opportunities." }, // Strategist
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define product features and prioritize tasks." }, // Product Manager
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Create illustrations and visual assets for various projects and media." }, // Illustrator
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Manage client relationships, address their needs, and handle project timelines." }, // Account Manager
  { tag: "Potential Task", description: "Curate art exhibitions and select artworks to be displayed in galleries." }, // Gallery Curator
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Conduct research on historical art movements and analyze art from different eras." }, // Art Historian
  { tag: "Potential Task", description: "Bring characters and objects to life through animation sequences." }, // Animator
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Design animated visuals and motion graphics for various digital platforms." }, // Motion Designer
  { tag: "Potential Task", description: "Create game concepts, mechanics, and levels for interactive experiences." }, // Game Designer
  { tag: "Potential Task", description: "Explore innovative technologies and implement them in creative projects." }, // Creative Technologist
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Lead creative teams, provide artistic direction, and ensure visual consistency." }, // Art Director
  { tag: "Day-to-day Work", description: "Write engaging and persuasive copy for advertisements, websites, or marketing materials." }, // Copywriter
];


export const projectsData = [
  {
    title: "Create a mural for Goryeb Children's Hospital",
    start: "AUG 06 2023",
    end: "SEP 17 2023",
    tags: ["Internship", "Art", "Painting"],
  },
  {
    title: "Create an immersive AR experience for Coachella",
    start: "JUL 06 2023",
    end: "DEC 17 2023",
    tags: ["Project", "Technology", "Design"],
  },
  {
    title: "Create an AR Mobile App for Coca-Cola",
    start: "JUL 06 2023",
    end: "DEC 17 2023",
    tags: ["Project", "Technology", "Design"],
  },
]